<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Innocent Musings of an Amateur Mind]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Innocent Musings of an Amateur Mind]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:46:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Amateur Mind]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>An Amateur Mind</h1><p>My life has been a continually rolling series of failures, fuck ups, and hospital beds. This definitely isn’t an instruction guide for happiness nor success, rather a somewhat shitty recounting of how I survived some of it and fucked up the rest.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/an-amateur-mind/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0648c6df-be0f-4ee7-be3e-0b169155c551</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:22:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The shackles of my humanity… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The shackles of my humanity… </h1><p>I am not a writer, though I write. I am not a philosopher, though I think. I am not a scientist, though I wonder. I love, I saunter, I reminisce. I do all these things and many more, though I am only defined by the boundaries set by my fears. My impending death cast thy fears asunder, abstaining my definition, releasing me of the shackles of my humanity.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/the-shackles-of-my-humanity/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d216239b-4e37-4164-b1b2-a76bdbcaad26</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:44:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Survival is the life of somebody worth saving… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Survival is the life of somebody worth saving… </h1><p>Survival is the life of somebody worth saving; I wasn’t that life. I didn’t want to survive, I ravaged, pillaged, and burned my way through. Life, to me, was a burning ember comprised of a genetic dead-end. I intended to blow on the ember making it burn as hot and as bright as it could. Burn, baby, burn…</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/survival-is-the-life-of-somebody-worth-saving/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8ab2c470-9094-494d-953a-f713879ac47b</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:43:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cry havoc and let slip the dogs of war… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Cry havoc and let slip the dogs of war… </h1><p>Growing up is hard for most, but the challenges I faced forced me to do most of it. When I’ve told my stories to a select few I get the impression that they thought I was this strong-willed kid that survived horrible things, almost heroically. I disagree, the truth is, I didn’t have a choice; which is why I struggled with my past for so long. The first 15 years of my life were a blur of pain and medications with a sprinkling of laughter and tears. I quietly understood that I was going to die, but that seemed like such an abstract idea at the time. Besides, which 13-year-old kid doesn’t think 30 years is super old. I think what shaped how I look at the world the most was the realization that the future is a noose on the necks of the unenlightened masses.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/cry-havoc-and-let-slip-the-dogs-of-war/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">018f754c-683b-48e8-95d2-bddf84178ee2</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:41:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[They drew first blood… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>They drew first blood… </h1><p>Endless hospital halls and the pervasive smell of sanitizer were staples of the memories of my childhood. I could not shake the feeling that I had missed some essential part of life, or maybe I just didn’t want to believe that this was all life was. I returned to Honduras changed; pain had forced me to grow up faster than even I wanted to, despite its advantages in dealing with my situation. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/they-drew-first-blood/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">40de0c8d-bcf6-44de-bd43-bdd155b30373</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:39:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Summa Omnium Veritatum… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Summa Omnium Veritatum… </h1><p>It was early on in my life that I learned lessons that, now I realize, take most humans a lifetime to learn; if ever. First lesson, pain is truth; most have never experienced the kind of life changing pain I’m referring to which is why I think sometimes it’s hard for me to relate to other hominids. This type of pain changes your perception of reality; for myself, it seemed I could just make out the edges of the curtain on reality; as if peeling it back would reveal the wizard pulling the levers behind it. If reality was this tenuous projection upon a thin veil, that everyone around me seemed blind to, then I was going to make it my own; king be the one-eyed man in the land of the blind.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/summa-omnium-veritatum/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">78bf4814-f859-4824-bc82-c208dc7a82a8</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:36:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Live or Die on this day… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Live or Die on this day… </h1><p>I got eight months of normalcy, or at least as normal as I could get. In those eight months my friendship with Francisco blossomed into what it is today, a brotherly bond. Then it started…</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/live-or-die-on-this-day/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b581345c-2851-4a00-895d-006c6a6f68c2</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:34:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[It is the privilege of lesser men to light the flame… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>It is the privilege of lesser men to light the flame… </h1><p>Growing up apart from society, confined within hospital walls, gave me an exception to what I consider its monopoly on conformity. I had to learn quickly and adapt. I spent my childhood learning this lesson. A lesson I thought I was done learning; and like most other times in life, upon self reflection, I realize how wrong I was.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/it-is-the-privilege-of-lesser-men-to-light-the-flame/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">358e080b-1514-4d8d-9673-a1555c6f06a8</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:33:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intelligent life?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Intelligent life?</h1><p>I was born on August 1983 in Tegucigalpa, Honduras…</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/intelligent-life/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3a00bd87-5ff8-4290-a950-7683da926354</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:31:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>