<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Innocent Musings of an Amateur Mind]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Innocent Musings of an Amateur Mind]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:44:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Amateur Mind]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>An Amateur Mind</h1><p>My life has been a continually rolling series of failures, fuck ups, and hospital beds. This definitely isn’t an instruction guide for happiness nor success, rather a somewhat shitty recounting of how I survived some of it and fucked up the rest.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b95380553fbc7e21f2fc938d5e72a9e99c7eecff.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/an-amateur-mind/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0648c6df-be0f-4ee7-be3e-0b169155c551</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The power of silence… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The power of silence… </h1><p>…then in one night of insomnia and scrambled thoughts, I was annoyed by all the lights in my bedroom. The years of inane hoarding of portals to my technological proclivities had finally come back to assault my senses. Awash in blinking status lights I arose groggy and irritated in a desperate pursuit of the greatest nerd tool of all, electrical tape. I attacked the photonic emitters mercilessly and with efficiency rarely seen outside elite military units. With the mission accomplished, darkness embraced me and my weary mind. A sardonic smirk across my face I lay down in a meager attempt at unconsciousness.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/92abf88f-b356-4fa0-8f8f-95b06eb4dd87.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/the-power-of-silence/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2cff4d9e-0eca-4c11-9bcd-ca3df27454a7</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:43:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The hardened levees of my solitude… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The hardened levees of my solitude… </h1><p>Leaving Honduras once more I could feel my whole body relax. My breaths felt deeper and more satisfying, my posture a little straighter, my attitude slightly relaxed. I barely spent a little over one year before graduating and leaving for college. On the flight to Miami I wasn’t sure what to think of my decision not just of attending Florida Tech in a small town such as Melbourne, but of accepting to major in Civil Engineering. It was a difficult decision, one I struggled with, and to this day consider a mistake.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/7c50473f0645d6949b02c54d48e6e51621cc52a4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/the-hardened-levees-of-my-solitude/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9164a72a-17d4-4c6f-9196-5c6430a0fba6</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:42:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I’m not afraid to fall… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>I’m not afraid to fall… </h1><p>I’m frustrated and sad. I question whether I am even capable of achieving the goals of my ambitions. I want to make a mark in history but can I? How do I regain a confidence I wasn’t even sure I had, and now long for? Logic and reason is how. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b6722545bdbd2d6879654ad0e206bbed755605fc.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/im-not-afraid-to-fall/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b9690cc2-d531-4401-8ef1-28e2b54bcc62</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:40:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An interesting posit of a fantasy for when my reality was unbearable… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>An interesting posit of a fantasy for when my reality was unbearable… </h1><p>I’m wrong. I’m not the victim of a genetic short stick from a universe hell-bent on my destruction. My mind bears the scars of constant threats to its sanity and my survival. These scars are not liabilities that should be carefully navigated around and treated as brain damage. These scars are my armor, my shield, the infrastructure that holds dearly the potential of my great future. I survived, but I want more than to be a survivor, that is too common a goal for the pain I suffered and my ambitions. The scars of my survival are the foundation for greatness. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/55ad2c8e5c449d4cb1b296f2b6bdeb68a37bf4c1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/an-interesting-posit-of-a-fantasy-for-when-my-reality-was-un/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2c5d2512-72f1-4ca9-ad7d-039166720261</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:39:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dr. Frankenstein’s monster… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Dr. Frankenstein’s monster… </h1><p>Two weeks after returning from the military academy something in me came to life. I could once more focus on the world around me, in the present, than lose myself in endless self-examination. I returned to Honduras to finish my senior year of high school, and I was ready to take it for all it was worth. Nothing seemed impossible, girls, crazy adventures, and the persistent need for an adrenaline rush. The world revealed itself for the game that it was, and I felt like I had the cheat codes. I was alive…</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/1cada81395636ad786d16e3754f501ed4d6ced10.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/dr-frankensteins-monster/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ad358c9d-3fcf-4655-bbeb-86dacd559e70</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:39:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The shackles of my humanity… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The shackles of my humanity… </h1><p>I am not a writer, though I write. I am not a philosopher, though I think. I am not a scientist, though I wonder. I love, I saunter, I reminisce. I do all these things and many more, though I am only defined by the boundaries set by my fears. My impending death cast thy fears asunder, abstaining my definition, releasing me of the shackles of my humanity.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/fcba85d6051b7533d631cca32f4c0814a84d0469.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/the-shackles-of-my-humanity/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d216239b-4e37-4164-b1b2-a76bdbcaad26</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:38:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Survival is the life of somebody worth saving… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Survival is the life of somebody worth saving… </h1><p>Survival is the life of somebody worth saving; I wasn’t that life. I didn’t want to survive, I ravaged, pillaged, and burned my way through. Life, to me, was a burning ember comprised of a genetic dead-end. I intended to blow on the ember making it burn as hot and as bright as it could. Burn, baby, burn…</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/cddc8fda29b6d612ce2a0d1b47eb9cb6f29fc6a3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/survival-is-the-life-of-somebody-worth-saving/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8ab2c470-9094-494d-953a-f713879ac47b</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:37:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cry havoc and let slip the dogs of war… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Cry havoc and let slip the dogs of war… </h1><p>Growing up is hard for most, but the challenges I faced forced me to do most of it. When I’ve told my stories to a select few I get the impression that they thought I was this strong-willed kid that survived horrible things, almost heroically. I disagree, the truth is, I didn’t have a choice; which is why I struggled with my past for so long. The first 15 years of my life were a blur of pain and medications with a sprinkling of laughter and tears. I quietly understood that I was going to die, but that seemed like such an abstract idea at the time. Besides, which 13-year-old kid doesn’t think 30 years is super old. I think what shaped how I look at the world the most was the realization that the future is a noose on the necks of the unenlightened masses.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8077c0d9a6ba3a7435adc40a367e4268e43930a4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/cry-havoc-and-let-slip-the-dogs-of-war/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">018f754c-683b-48e8-95d2-bddf84178ee2</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:36:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[They drew first blood… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>They drew first blood… </h1><p>Endless hospital halls and the pervasive smell of sanitizer were staples of the memories of my childhood. I could not shake the feeling that I had missed some essential part of life, or maybe I just didn’t want to believe that this was all life was. I returned to Honduras changed; pain had forced me to grow up faster than even I wanted to, despite its advantages in dealing with my situation. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ce4e45d7b2ea542fad8aff08fd954579496b2ecd.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/they-drew-first-blood/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">40de0c8d-bcf6-44de-bd43-bdd155b30373</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:35:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>