<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Innocent Musings of an Amateur Mind]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Innocent Musings of an Amateur Mind]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:09:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Amateur Mind]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>An Amateur Mind</h1><p>My life has been a continually rolling series of failures, fuck ups, and hospital beds. This definitely isn’t an instruction guide for happiness nor success, rather a somewhat shitty recounting of how I survived some of it and fucked up the rest.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/an-amateur-mind/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0648c6df-be0f-4ee7-be3e-0b169155c551</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:22:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Why?</h1><p>How the fuck did I get into this mess!?! Despite knowing the answer, I kept asking myself as I stared aimlessly at the door in my unlit room. I was alone again, in the literal sense as I always feel alone anyway. Burned my way through another social circle out of sheer boredom, and in the process alienated someone I should have cared about but those emotions never seemed to align within me. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/why/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">19f82d53-51de-4cad-8c5e-bf22858584f8</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[You only need to succeed today… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>You only need to succeed today… </h1><p>First I was afraid of the needles, but my skin grew callused and scarred. Then I was afraid of the results, but my mind isolated emotion and empathy. Then I realized my enemy wasn’t pain, emotion, or the humans; it was me. I have the choice to keep going or to give up and that is incredibly empowering. Do or die, fail or win…every day is a choice.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/you-only-need-to-succeed-today/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b70777ea-4561-4825-a629-68cd2870a16a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Champagne wishes and caviar dreams… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Champagne wishes and caviar dreams… </h1><p>Watching the news, reading the papers, and seeing what could be called humans, if only for lack of a better word descriptive of their semblance to encyclopedic references. Encrusted in the smoldering remnants of what this ironically blind species considered the pinnacle of nature whilst blissfully ignoring the evolutionary dead end sign next to the geologically fresh crater of the previous proprietors, and I humbly realize that my fellow mammals, or hairless monkeys, as I like to call ourselves, that drafted that rallying cry, “home of the free, land of the brave.”, that every mass of peoples in the past, in one mutation or another, has adopted, were either unbelievably naïve or nonchalantly attempting to discredit evolution as his fellow man missed the irony in the signs of the coming end.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/875b41b23e1dfbeeee3046b9a0607b618ea011e7.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/champagne-wishes-and-caviar-dreams/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a766f32a-e67c-46cc-bc4f-7451370f1217</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ignorance is the path of the wise… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ignorance is the path of the wise… </h1><p>When I started down the path of entrepreneurship I had no idea how much I would have to sacrifice, I don’t think most first time entrepreneurs really do. Worst even, I don’t think it would have mattered; I was dying, I didn’t care. It still shocks me to this day how little thought I really gave to the consequences of my actions. Regardless, down the rabbit hole I went; blind to the reality that surrounded me.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/ignorance-is-the-path-of-the-wise/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ceafe06a-e2cb-4785-80d6-abb6d72490f1</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[10AM with Strangers… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>10AM with Strangers… </h1><p>Sitting in a small room at 10AM with strangers I realize the fear in every beat of my heart. I feel like I’m about to fall off a cliff, and keep wondering if perhaps accepting death would just be easier than the constant struggles that have defined my life.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/10am-with-strangers/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7e1c6200-98da-4d08-85ea-67dfbe629433</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An interesting posit of a fantasy for when my reality was unbearable… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>An interesting posit of a fantasy for when my reality was unbearable… </h1><p>I’m wrong. I’m not the victim of a genetic short stick from a universe hell-bent on my destruction. My mind bears the scars of constant threats to its sanity and my survival. These scars are not liabilities that should be carefully navigated around and treated as brain damage. These scars are my armor, my shield, the infrastructure that holds dearly the potential of my great future. I survived, but I want more than to be a survivor, that is too common a goal for the pain I suffered and my ambitions. The scars of my survival are the foundation for greatness. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/an-interesting-posit-of-a-fantasy-for-when-my-reality-was-un/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2c5d2512-72f1-4ca9-ad7d-039166720261</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I’m not afraid to fall… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>I’m not afraid to fall… </h1><p>I’m frustrated and sad. I question whether I am even capable of achieving the goals of my ambitions. I want to make a mark in history but can I? How do I regain a confidence I wasn’t even sure I had, and now long for? Logic and reason is how. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/im-not-afraid-to-fall/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b9690cc2-d531-4401-8ef1-28e2b54bcc62</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The hardened levees of my solitude… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The hardened levees of my solitude… </h1><p>Leaving Honduras once more I could feel my whole body relax. My breaths felt deeper and more satisfying, my posture a little straighter, my attitude slightly relaxed. I barely spent a little over one year before graduating and leaving for college. On the flight to Miami I wasn’t sure what to think of my decision not just of attending Florida Tech in a small town such as Melbourne, but of accepting to major in Civil Engineering. It was a difficult decision, one I struggled with, and to this day consider a mistake.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/the-hardened-levees-of-my-solitude/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9164a72a-17d4-4c6f-9196-5c6430a0fba6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The power of silence… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The power of silence… </h1><p>…then in one night of insomnia and scrambled thoughts, I was annoyed by all the lights in my bedroom. The years of inane hoarding of portals to my technological proclivities had finally come back to assault my senses. Awash in blinking status lights I arose groggy and irritated in a desperate pursuit of the greatest nerd tool of all, electrical tape. I attacked the photonic emitters mercilessly and with efficiency rarely seen outside elite military units. With the mission accomplished, darkness embraced me and my weary mind. A sardonic smirk across my face I lay down in a meager attempt at unconsciousness.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/the-power-of-silence/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2cff4d9e-0eca-4c11-9bcd-ca3df27454a7</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>