<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Innocent Musings of an Amateur Mind]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Innocent Musings of an Amateur Mind]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:11:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Amateur Mind]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>An Amateur Mind</h1><p>My life has been a continually rolling series of failures, fuck ups, and hospital beds. This definitely isn’t an instruction guide for happiness nor success, rather a somewhat shitty recounting of how I survived some of it and fucked up the rest.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/an-amateur-mind/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0648c6df-be0f-4ee7-be3e-0b169155c551</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:22:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The right spark… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The right spark… </h1><p>My insecurities, my impending death, the world and everyone in it washed away from my mind as I focused on my creation. Nothing else mattered. I left college that summer a curious boy and returned a changed man, still immature and reclusive but different none the less. I could not concentrate on anything else. I tried to ignore the siren’s call and tie my attention to the mast of my mind’s ship; like Odysseus I failed. College was no longer the place for me.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/the-right-spark/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8030c7f0-9e2d-4eb8-8343-e07468d7bc37</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[It’s not easy being green… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>It’s not easy being green… </h1><p>Growing up I always felt different. It was obvious to me that I didn’t fit in, despite my endless attempts to pretend to. Impostor syndrome, they call it, or so I read. Not sure if that’s because of my time spent away for normal social interactions with the humans or I’m just the result of an electrochemical physiological imbalance due to abhorrent genetic expressions. Truth is I’ve felt this way every day of my life.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/its-not-easy-being-green/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ae90fb70-bca6-47e7-909a-baacad970adb</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Human?</h1><p>What is a human?</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/human/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ea296a59-774d-4d8e-ae54-13488017575c</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The corners of my mind… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The corners of my mind… </h1><p>Playing with computers and solving problems I get little whispers of happiness but they’re always fleeting. I feel like a junkie running from one situation to the other trying to get my fix. It’s the silence in between fixes that always gets me; the ramblings from the corners of my mind.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/the-corners-of-my-mind/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">04984b15-edf9-4c74-902f-7835fe524ff5</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The waves of loneliness crash upon the hardened levees of my solitude… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The waves of loneliness crash upon the hardened levees of my solitude… </h1><p>No matter the people or my surroundings I’ve always felt alone. Human relationships feel so temporary to me. It could be a self-fulfilling bias. I presume relationships are temporary therefore make them temporary. Equally, I don’t get attached because I don’t feel connected and I don’t feel connected because I don’t get attached. In the end, the result is the same; solitude.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/the-waves-of-loneliness-crash-upon-the-hardened-levees-of-my/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">63aed437-d46d-4b21-88f7-e34edd16647f</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Why?</h1><p>How the fuck did I get into this mess!?! Despite knowing the answer, I kept asking myself as I stared aimlessly at the door in my unlit room. I was alone again, in the literal sense as I always feel alone anyway. Burned my way through another social circle out of sheer boredom, and in the process alienated someone I should have cared about but those emotions never seemed to align within me. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/why/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">19f82d53-51de-4cad-8c5e-bf22858584f8</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[You only need to succeed today… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>You only need to succeed today… </h1><p>First I was afraid of the needles, but my skin grew callused and scarred. Then I was afraid of the results, but my mind isolated emotion and empathy. Then I realized my enemy wasn’t pain, emotion, or the humans; it was me. I have the choice to keep going or to give up and that is incredibly empowering. Do or die, fail or win…every day is a choice.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/you-only-need-to-succeed-today/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b70777ea-4561-4825-a629-68cd2870a16a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Champagne wishes and caviar dreams… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Champagne wishes and caviar dreams… </h1><p>Watching the news, reading the papers, and seeing what could be called humans, if only for lack of a better word descriptive of their semblance to encyclopedic references. Encrusted in the smoldering remnants of what this ironically blind species considered the pinnacle of nature whilst blissfully ignoring the evolutionary dead end sign next to the geologically fresh crater of the previous proprietors, and I humbly realize that my fellow mammals, or hairless monkeys, as I like to call ourselves, that drafted that rallying cry, “home of the free, land of the brave.”, that every mass of peoples in the past, in one mutation or another, has adopted, were either unbelievably naïve or nonchalantly attempting to discredit evolution as his fellow man missed the irony in the signs of the coming end.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/875b41b23e1dfbeeee3046b9a0607b618ea011e7.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/champagne-wishes-and-caviar-dreams/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a766f32a-e67c-46cc-bc4f-7451370f1217</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ignorance is the path of the wise… ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ignorance is the path of the wise… </h1><p>When I started down the path of entrepreneurship I had no idea how much I would have to sacrifice, I don’t think most first time entrepreneurs really do. Worst even, I don’t think it would have mattered; I was dying, I didn’t care. It still shocks me to this day how little thought I really gave to the consequences of my actions. Regardless, down the rabbit hole I went; blind to the reality that surrounded me.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/innocent-musings-of-an-amateur-mind/ignorance-is-the-path-of-the-wise/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ceafe06a-e2cb-4785-80d6-abb6d72490f1</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>